{"response_code": 0, "results": [{"category": "Entertainment: Video Games", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "hard", "question": "In &quot;Portal 2&quot;, Cave Johnson started out Aperture Science as a shower curtain company.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"category": "Entertainment: Video Games", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy", "question": "The PlayStation was originally a joint project between Sega and Sony that was a Sega Genesis with a disc drive.", "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}, {"category": "Entertainment: Video Games", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy", "question": "In the game &quot;Subnautica&quot;, a &quot;Spadefish&quot; will attack you.", "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}, {"category": "Entertainment: Video Games", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "hard", "question": "The names of Roxas&#039;s Keyblades in Kingdom Hearts are &quot;Oathkeeper&quot; and &quot;Oblivion&quot;.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"category": "Entertainment: Video Games", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy", "question": "In Pok&eacute;mon, Bulbasaur is the only starter pokemon that is a Grass/Poison type.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"category": "Entertainment: Video Games", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy", "question": "The Konami Code is known as Up, Up, Down, Down, Left, Right, Right, Left, B, A, Start.", "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}, {"category": "Entertainment: Video Games", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium", "question": "In Portal, the Companion Cube&#039;s ARE sentient.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"category": "Entertainment: Video Games", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium", "question": "In &quot;Starbound&quot;, the track played by the Decorated Music Box is named &quot;Atlas&quot;.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"category": "Entertainment: Video Games", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy", "question": "The game &quot;Pocket Morty&quot; has a Morty called &quot;Pocket Mortys Morty&quot;?", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"category": "Entertainment: Video Games", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy", "question": "The game &quot;Jetpack Joyride&quot; was created by &quot;Redbrick Studios&quot;.", "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}]}